<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<page subtitle=": privacy statement" lastupdated="$Date: 2002/10/24 21:37:07 $">
<menuoption href="./who.html" caption="Who are we?" />
<menuoption href="./why.html" caption="Why use us?" />
<menuoption href="./how.html" caption="How can we help YOUR business?" />
<menuoption href="./contactus.html" caption="Contact us" />
<menuoption href="./privacy.html" caption="Privacy" />

<bodytext>
<bodytextheading>Discmark Data Supplies: Privacy Statement</bodytextheading>
<bodytextpara>
	<paratext>
This privacy statement is designed to inform you how we collect and use
personal information and how you can control the uses to which it is put.
	</paratext>
</bodytextpara>
<bodytextpara>
<paraheading>User Registration Information</paraheading>
	<paratext>
Most of the discmark.com web site is accessible without giving us any personal
information. However there are some parts where we require you to register
your details before we can allow you access. When you register we ask for
information about yourself, such as name, postal address, e-mail address
and other personal data. This data is added to our records and retained
for future use. You may view or amend this information at any time by
visiting the amend account page.
	</paratext>
</bodytextpara>
<bodytextpara>
<paraheading>Receiving Communications from us</paraheading>
	<paratext>
During the registration process you will be given a choice as to
whether you would like Discmark Data Supplies or our business partners
to contact you in the future. This is an "opt-in" process. If you
opt-in, we may send you company information, software update
announcements or other promotional materials. If you later decide
that you would not like to receive these communications, you may
opt out any time by visiting the amend account page.
	</paratext>
</bodytextpara>
<bodytextpara>
<paraheading>Security</paraheading>
	<paratext>
We never sell our customers' information or provide it to others
without making it clear that we intend to do so at the time the
information is collected.
We will take appropriate steps to protect the information you
share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure.
	</paratext>
</bodytextpara>
<bodytextpara>
<paraheading>Cookies and Other Browser Information</paraheading>
	<paratext>
Our site automatically captures IP addresses. We use IP addresses to help
diagnose problems with our server, to administer our website and to help
ensure the security of your interaction with the website.
Those parts of the elcel.com web site that require registration
also require your browser to accept cookies. A cookie is a small
amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and
sometimes stored on your computer's hard drive.
We use cookies so that you do not have to log on to the site more than once.
	</paratext>
</bodytextpara>
<bodytextpara>
<paraheading>About Links to Other Sites</paraheading>
	<paratext>
This site contains links to other sites. Discmark Data Supplies does
not control the privacy policies or the contents of sites that can be
reached through links from discmark.com. If you have questions about
the privacy policies of linked sites, please contact those companies directly.
	</paratext>
</bodytextpara>
<bodytextpara>
<paraheading>Further Information</paraheading>
	<paratext>
If you require further information or have a specific request regarding
your privacy you can email us at privacy@discmark.com.
	</paratext>
</bodytextpara>
</bodytext>
</page>
